The prosecutor's office has investigated
the employees of K Corporation for tax evasion.
They've also extended their investigation
of slush funds and off-shore tax evasion as well.
Are you planning to hand this over to Se Gwang?
The Ahn Do Hoon file that you wanted
is in the safe deposit box.
When he becomes a threat to us,
it might help you.
This will hurt not only the K Corporation,
but you as well.
Listen to it when you have time.
It's the testimony of the truck driver. It should be interesting.
Why didn't you think about it when you dumped my father?
You don't have enough evidence, what do you want?
Should I destroy Jo Min Hyuk completely?
It won't end here.
I'll bring you to court, no matter what it takes.
In the place you worshiped so much,
you'll have to confess to your crime.
I can't... I can't let it end here.
What? Are you scared?
Why is Mr. Ahn here?
The painting bribe of Shina Gallery that Mr. Choi was engaged in.
If I reveal those who were involved, it'll cause a big stir.
But don't worry. I can stop it.
- What are you doing? - This company that your father has built
might collapse.
Listen to me. I'm the most qualified person to defend you.
I'm the one who can protect Mr. Jo.
Ahn Do Hoon fomr the Legal Team of the K Corporation,
What are you going to do?
What are you doing here?
Both you and I are in danger.
Choose between living together, or dying together.
- Shin Se Yeon! - You, the K Corporation,
Se Yeon, and Se Yeon's father will be in trouble.
Ah! Let's not forget Yoo Jung. I know her more than anyone.
She'll blame herself for what happened.
She'll be upset.
I told you to stay away from Yoo Jung.
You have to choose between your company and the woman that you love so much.
You'll choose the K Corporation in the end.
Can you still say that we're different?
I want to ask you something.
What are you doing?
I'm sure you're well aware of what I'm doing.
What are you going to do now?
- Yoo Jung, listen to me! - Are you okay?
No matter what Mr. Ahn said.
- Do what you should do. - Sir.
- You trust me, right? - Yes.
I'll not be defeated that easily.
Trust me and go.
I told you,
we are different.
I'm going to visit your father.
The news of our break up will be printed tomorrow.
Are you really going to do this?
Is she that important to you?
I'm breaking off this engagement.
I'll be responsible for it.
I'll do my best not to hurt you.
- I'm sorry it took so long. - Min Hyuk!
Bring back the Se Yeon I once knew.
Being destructive and irrational like this
isn't you.
You used Yoo Jung, and now Se Yeon?
Do not hurt the Shina Foundation.
You're the one who let this happen.
If anything happens to Se Yeon, it's your fault.
And to the K Corporation. You'll regret it.
I won't. If I stop Yoo Jung
to save myself, that I'll regret.
You're first the heir of the K Corporation
then Yoo Jung's man.
Don't forget that the K Corporation is in danger.
I'm not going down alone.
If I have to, I'll take you down with me.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
What about you?
As long as you're okay.
I'll tell the press that I'm not going to marry Se Yeon tomorrow.
I made my choice. You don't have to worry.
You can just stay with me, okay?
It's a breaking news if it's true.
- Are you going to be okay?? - If I worried about me,
I wouldn't have done it.
I'm not slandering the K Corporation
to do some illegal business for management right.
President Jo
and Jo Min Hyuk
has been accumulating slush funds and bribing.
As a prosecutor, Ahn Do Hoon investigated the K Corporation's illegal activities.
He joined the K Corporation after he resigned...
Yes. President Jo doesn't know about this.
I stopped the news about the breakup.
- Father! - Don't ever that kind of woman in front of me again.
She is not that kind of woman to me.
- She is... - Are you going to marry a girl,
who was involved with that bastard?
You idiot.
- He's here! He's here! - Mr. Jo! Mr. Jo!
Excuse me, could you tell us what happened?
The information regardign Shina Foundation were released,
- Any comment? - Any comment?
Please tell us.
Is what Mr. Ahn said true?
Mr. Ahn didn't come to work today.
- What the hell are you doing? - Sorry.
Call a press conference and prepare our statement.
Yes, sir!
Kwang Soo, let's visit Gwang Min.
I have to do something about this.
- What are you doing? - That's what I want to ask you.
I told you. I wouldn't go to jail alone.
I'll go to jail with Jo Min Hyuk, who you want to protect so badly.
Stop it. Stop it right now.
Try if you can.
It won't be easy.
I've only revealed the truth.
The truth? I can reveal the truth as well.
About who you really are.
Get out!
Attend the cross-examination tomorrow.
Wow! Kang Yoo Jung.
I'm glad my hard work of following you around paid off.
See!
I came because I knew you'd be worried.
But, it's because of me.
Don't say that.
Just tell me that ‘everything will be okay.'
‘Everything will be okay.' Say it!
Everything will be okay.
Good. Since you said so, I'm not worried anymore.
What happened?
My father was here.
He's very concerned about his reputation. Don't mention this to anyone, please.
I didn't expose the Sina Foundation.
The things that they're investigating...
That's all right.
Look at you, how can you be all right?
I can stop it now if you want.
What if I stop now?
Can you leave with me?
You said you'd love to.
Let's go.
You can do what you want and forget this whole thing.
Thank you. Thanks to you, I'm really getting married to Min Hyuk.
I prevented your father from leaving the hospital.
Tomorrow, tell your father that you'll marry Se Yeon as planned.
Get out!
You won't be happy if you oppose your father.
I said get out.
I took care of you after your mother left.
Are you going to regret losing your father for a girl like that for the rest of your life?
For a woman like you, my father
abandoned my mother.
Stop pretending that you don't know anything.
I came here because your mother wanted me to.
I'm just a unfamous singer, your father do like me,
but that's it.
As you know, you mother wasn't happy here.
She didn't like living as the lady of the K Corporation.
She asked me to take care of you and your father.
- What are you talkign about? - Yes.
Don't believe, don't believe that kind of silly love exists.
Tell your father yourself.
He won't listen to me anymore.
Mr. Jo wanted me to give you a ride.
Thank you.
He's busy today.
Really?
Let's go.
I did have Mr. Kang Woo Chul in my car that day.
But when I stopped for a minute, he disappeared.
The bracelet he was wearing was gone.
Not a lot of people know what that is.
The person who gave my father the bracelet might have taken it off.
Leaving her sick father home alone, Ms. Kang was drinking at a club.
She called me later and said that her father was missing.
I went there to do her a favor.
The owner of the store saw my father that day,
she said my fatehr looked normal and even recognized her on that day.
What did my father tell you
that scared you enough to dump him in the street?
This is just the beginning.
You'll have to tell me what happened to my father on that day.
No matter how hard you try, you can't prove anything.
You're wasting your time.
No matter how long it takes,
I'll make you confess your sins from your own mouth.
Do you know what the common illusion that people like you have?
Believing that truth and justice always win.
Don't be silly. That doesn't happen.
Don't you get it?
Only those who have power can protect their loved ones and get justice.
That's why we ended up like this.
How do you become a man like this?
I thought I was the one who liked publicity. I can't compare with you.
Do you decide to be a just man?
Or are you just a whistle blower who betrayed his own company?
What are you talking about?
People are talking and it's all over the news.
I told you that Min Hyuk isn't a pushover.
Who you could easily take on.
I didn't do anything. Jo Min Hyuk broke the law.
If he broke the law, he'll be punished,
but that's not my case.
That girl was the hit-and-run driver, right?
When this is over, I'll volunteer for your investigation.
It's alleged that Ahn Do Hoon,
who revealed the K Corporation's illegal activities, actually embezzled 6.5 billion KRW from a branch
that the K Corporation founded in Hong Kong.
Mr. Jo Min Hyuk, the heir of the K Corporation
said during the press conference today that...
Have you been here before?
It's pretty high.
It's a good height to fall from.
6.5 billion.
I didn't take the money. It went into constructing your building.
You're right.
But there's no evidence of that.
Gwang Min is careful.
He didn't leave any evidence.
Just like you.
Congratulations on your marriage.
Congressman Shin slapped Se Yeon yesterday.
You're the one who made her life miserable.
I have nothing more to lose. Yoo Jung said,
the more you own, the more you worried.
You have a lot more to lose than me.
I wanted to take it away from you, but it's tired.
That's why I'm taking you down with me.
I have no intention of going down with you.
Let's say that I embezzled 6.5 billion KRW.
Let's destroy the K Corporation and the Shina Foundation together with me.
Your father will spend some time in jail.
You, Se Yeon and Congressman Shin
will have to be investigated.
You alone can't destroy our company that easily.
I'm not alone.
People who are sick of rich guys will join me.
Do you think it'll make a difference?
I thought you were smart,
but you're an idealist.
On the night of the accident...
I was driving, not Yoo Jung.
Do you want me to repeat it so you can record it?
Yoo Jung didn't kill her. I did.
Yoo Jung volunteered to go to jail for me.
I tried to stop her, but she wouldn't listen.
Ahn Do Hoon.
She's that kind of a girl.
She gave up her own life because of love.
The files and the recording.
Do whatever you want with them.
But I'm curious.
Do you think you can protect the woman,
that I was unable to protect?
Stay away from Yoo Jung.
I will.
If I destroy you, she'll ruin herself.
You poor bastard!
You don't know what you've lost, yet.
I hope the person Yoo Jung once loved
wasn't this same bastard I see right now.
Father, you're still not well enough.
You can't do this, father.
Do you expect me to lie here
and watch you destroy my company? You bastard.
Father!
I've been working for 60 years with this body.
It's no wonder why my body can't bear anymore.
I've made enough money,
but I've always bowed down to authority.
I only wanted one thing from you.
To stand up to authority.
That's why you need Congressman Shin.
You know that I'm not that excellent.
What I want to protect
is that girl.
Love is good.
But time will change everything.
You'll forget her over time.
Your mother,
she is the daughter of a gambler who owned a small inn.
Her father brought her to me to pay his debt.
I built her a small hotel,
and that's how the K Hotel started.
During the opening ceremony, she smiled so brightly.
That's the last time I saw your mother smile.
Father.
I can't stand to lose the K Hotel just because of you.
I'm not greedy.
I'm asking you as the boss of the K Hotel,
to protect the K Hotel on my behalf.
Don't make Gwang Min's sacrifice be in vain.
Please.
I said I'd see you again.
Look! The house is empty.
I sent my daughter abroad for a while.
Have you seen the news?
If Min Hyuk cancel the engagement with Se Yeon, the situation will become worse.
Min Hyuk won't be safe, either.
Investigations, trials, and jail.
Do you want him to become a convict, just like you?
Is that how you love Min Hyuk?
Madam.
Min Hyuk's father is very sick.
If Min Hyuk leave,
his father's condition might get worse.
Min Hyuk doesn't have the luxury of pursuing his own happiness while abandoning his father.
You know that, right?
Do I have to say more?
When Min Hyuk is happy, he'll scold others.
When he's grateful he'll get snappy.
But,
He seldom shows his depression.
I know he's depressed about his mother's death.
You're his mother at the moment.
Please take good care of him.
It's me. Are you free tomorrow?
Is this the place you want to go with me?
I wasn't able to be at his deathbed.
It hurts me when I think how lonely he must've been.
I know how it feels
to desert my own father
because of the one I loved.
I know how regertful it is.
Yoo Jung.
How can I ask you to abandon your own father to be with me?
Stop! Stop saying it.
Look at you.
You're already in great agony. But you never say it.
Don't worry about me.
I went to the restaurant. The workers are worried about our company.
If you abandon them because of me,
you're doing a terrible thing to the workers who've been working hard for you.
I can't let that happen.
I don't want to feel guilty to those people.
I don't care about them.
I'm not a great person.
I just want to protect my girl.
No! I can't!
I told you that I only want you to be with me.
Stop saying the nonsense.
It sucks.
I have a interview. Make it quick.
Kwang Soo.
Destroy the files and the tape.
Yoo Jung.
Play with me.
You want me to skip off my work?
Just today.
Just today...
I'll play with you just today.
What wish did you make?
It's a secret.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
Fresh octopus.
It's fresh, buy some.
I'll give you a discount.
Fried Rice Cake again?
You know I don't like spicy food.
Just try it.
It's not spicy.
It's delicious.
I think I hired a good employee.
After we arranged everything,
can we live somewhere like this?
Shall we?
Don't make such an expression.
Smile.
Let's make today a happy memory.
Sir.
Aren't we going back?
I guess we should.
We've come too far.
It's hard to get back today.
I wish today would never end.
That may be boring.
So,
let's keep the memory till tomorrow.
Till tomorrow.
Can people live without love?
He was sipping his peppermint tea
instead of answering the question.
Why?
I'll stop here.
What did he say?
Is that all?
If you want to know,
read it
after I leave.
No.
I want you to read it for me.
I can't see your face while reading.
Just like this.
Can we stay like this for a while?
I think what my grandpa said before his 70s
is right,
People can't live
without love.
You asked me to love you.
How?
Yoo Jung!
How can this be love?
It hurts so much.
I can't stand it.
Is that love?
It's love.
When you miss someong,
the pain and loneliness are also love.
I think,
you seem to be suffered a lot.
You haven't eaten, right?
Ja Yeong.
I did the right thing,
right?
How can I be with him?
I can't do that, right?
So...
I did the right thing letting him go,
right?
Yes.
You did the right thing.
Are you sure?
Why can't I hold back my tears?
If you don't cry after letting someone go,
that'd be even stranger.
Tear this dress up
for me.
Did you know that your son embezzled 6.5 billion KRW?
We don't know anything. My son is a good man.
Madam, where is your son now?
Go away! Go!
Just one more thing to ask.
Go away. Come on.
Please answer it.
Just answer it.
Damn it.
What's going on?
You made Min Hyuk break up with her.
Thank you.
Are you happy now?
I told you
I had to have him at least once.
Yoo Jung.
Thanks to you, business is going well.
What a pity.
Thank you.
Yoo Jung, let's talk outside.
Why should I go outside?
Do Hoon will be here soon.
Get out!
We have customers here.
Why?
You're worried about your lawyer son?
How dare you?
Why don't you think about my dad?
Your son abandoned my father in the street,
and let him die after wandering away in his bare feet.
Don't make things up.
Take her out.
She's botHae Ring the customers.
I'm telling you the truth, how can you pretend nothing happened?
Bring back my father!
Yoo Jung, let's talk outside.
You don't believe it?
That's reasonable.
I couldn't believe it at first.
Mother...
You hated when I called you ‘mother.'
Madam
I'm here to ask your son what happened.
Get out!
Don't you book another room?
Cancel the honeymoon.
I don't want to go.
Se Yeon.
Are you enjoying this?
I'm not.
I didn't do this for fun.
I need to change. Can you excuse me?
Okay. Get some rest.
Married couples can divorce,
but you two only dated for a few years.
How dare you try to ruin my son's life?
You killed someone. Remember?
Stop. That's all gone.
Someone died. How can we forget?
Right.
You can't just forget about someone who you killed.
Since you know that, why are you here?
Do you still believe it was me?
What?
Don't pretend that you didn't know.
I just bought the car,
but Do Hoon drove it all the time.
You remember the day after the accident.
When I get the key from you.
What are you talking about?
Don't you understand?
Should I tell those people outside?
You! I've been patient enough. How dare you?
That's enough. I've had enough of it.
You have had enough of it?
What about your son who hit someone
and let her die and left my father to die?
How long should he be locked up for?
Longer than me, I guess.
Are you crazy?
No.
I'm saner than I've ever been.
What are you afraid of?
Go tell those reporters.
Stop!
Why should I stop?
Attention! I have something to say about the great lawyer Ahn Do Hoon.
- Mr. Ahn.- Mr. Ahn.
- Please answer the question. - Mr. Ahn.
Get out.
I said stop. Stop.
That's enough.
What?
San...
Don't you want to see him?
Your son.
Don't you miss him?